GOVIND POTDAR

Contact

Address:

50 Housing board colony, Dewas (M.P)

Phone:

+91 6265328168

Email:

govindpotdar2001@gmail.com

Website:

https://govindpotdar.github.io/hey

Languages

Hindi English Bengali

Summary

Specializing in backend development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, Python, Ruby.

Skill

- C, C++, PHP, Python, JavaScript, Ruby
- Codeigniter, ROR
- HTML,CSS

Experience

Junior Software Developer - 2022-01 to Current Gems Essence Infotech Pvt. Ltd., Indore

- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.
- Collaborated with project managers to select ambitious, but realistic coding milestones on pre-release software project development.

Software Developer Intern - 2021-02 to 2021-07 Quickensol IT Solutions., Pune

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Work with senior developer to manage large, complex projects for clients.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for back end.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.

Education

- B.tech from Malwa Institute of Science and Technology, Indore (M.P) in Computer Science (2018-2022) having CGPA of 7.7
- Senior Secondary from Board of Secondary Education, Madhya Pradesh, Bhopal with 78.6% in year 2018.
- High School from Board of Secondary Education, Madhya Pradesh, Bhopal with 64% in year 2016.